# Tiffany Bouchard

Full-Stack Developer

I am fuelled by challenge and driven to work with a team to build amazing experiences that enrich lives. I strive to use my curiosity and passion for technology to actualize innovative and creative concepts while applying quality UX and technical design.

## Experience

May - July 2020

## **Student - General Assembly Toronto**

- -Full-time student in the Software Engineering Immersive program including over 400 hours of training over 12 weeks
- -Completed three individual and collaborative full-stack projects incorporating technical skills learned
  - Chef Technical blog platform for tutorials
  - How Risky? A COVID-19 activity risk assessment app
  - Forkpitch A review platform for music reviews

Feb 2019 - Jan 2020

## Server & Supervisor - Otto's Berlin Döner

- -Performed end of day tasks including cash-out routine and counting till
- -Ensured front-of-house staff provided high-quality customer service and promoted a positive team atmosphere
- -Built strong relationships with customers, coworkers and management

March 2015 - Nov 2018

# Lifeguard, Instructor and Coach – City of Toronto

- -Promoted a safe environment and provided outstanding customer service to patrons
- -Displayed the ability to act quickly and calmly under pressure, individually and as a team
- -Cultivated positive relationships with participants

## Contact

tiffnbouchard@gmail.com 647-381-1429

linkedin.com/in/tiffany-bouchard/ github.com/tiffbouchard tiffbouchard.com

#### Education

Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly Toronto 2020

Philosophy & Criminology (HBA) University of Toronto 2016-2020

## **Languages & Frameworks**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, jQuery, Express, Bootstrap, React, Next.js, Python, Django, SQL, Mongoose

#### Tools

Git, GitHub, Heroku, Netlify, Vercel, Command Line, Figma

## **Databases**

PostgreSQL, MongoDB

## Methodologies/Techniques

Object Oriented Programming, MVC Pattern, AJAX, Responsive Design, User Stories, Wireframing, ERD's

### **Side Projects/Works in Progress**

- -Ojos eCommerce shop
- -lome Portfolio management app, building with a team of developers and UX designers
- LinenWay Redesigning/ rebuilding eCommerce for client with a team of developers and UX designers